"Readiness: Unsatisfactory.
Follows direction: Barely.
Attitude: A little too much.
Overall: Not only will he
probably die in a fiery inferno...
...his incessant whining would
most certainly spoil everyone else's day."
(Leonard:)You know what, I'm so tired
I can't even think straight. I'm going home.
Can one of you
give this nutbag a ride later?
(Sheldon:)You can't go home.
You have to take me to the dentist at 4:00.
- Oh. Can't you take the bus to the dentist?
- Of course I can.
It's coming back under the effects
of the anesthesia that's the problem.
(Sheldon:)Two years ago,
after a deep gum cleaning...
(Sheldon:)...I thought I got on a bus but somehow
wound up on a booze cruise to Mexico.
- They put you under for a cleaning?
- Yeah, they have to. I'm a biter.
Okay, whatever. Sheldon, I'm exhausted.
I'm not taking you to the dentist.
(Sheldon:)Wrong, sir. Wrong. Under Section 37B
of the Roommate Agreement...